(Howard:)she could literally sleep
with his own father in his own bed
(Howard:)and post the video to YouTube,
and he'd still buy her flowers
(Howard:)and ask her to be his bride.
(Raj:)He's right.
But in my defense,
if we could survive that,
(Raj:)we could survive anything.
(Bernadette:)Well, if you're sure you want
to do this, it's only coffee.
(Bernadette:)Just relax and see what happens.
(Raj:)-Well, can I say she looks nice?
-Sure.
(Raj:)Can I tell her I miss her?
(Bernadette:)Maybe, if she asks.
(Raj:)Can I show her
an oil painting I made of us
(Raj:)surrounded by our children
and grandchildren?
(Bernadette:)I'd save that for the second date.
(Raj:)Good, good,
'cause no matter how hard I try,
I cannot get the twins to lock alike.
(Penny:)What are you doing?
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm just trying to find
the stupid next of kin
(Leonard:)to this stupid video store owner,
so I can return the DVD